qualquantsignals.com 2018-02-13

# QualQuant Signals – Ideas & Insights - Privacy Policy

## **Website Privacy Statement**

In this Web Site Privacy Statement (“statement”), we, QualQuant Signals, headquartered in Lyndhurst, New Jersey, USA provide information about how we collect, use and transfer personally identifiable data from you, a web site visitor to web sites that we operate (collectively the “site”).

#### **Scope**

This statement covers data collected through the site. This statement does not cover any other data collection or processing, including, without limitation, data collection practices of other web pages to which QualQuant Signals links or data processing practices of users of our service. When QualQuant Signals refers to this statement in notices and consent requests related to surveys, special-purpose web pages or otherwise, this statement applies as modified in the particular notice or consent request (e.g., with respect to types of data collected or purposes of collection).

#### **Types of Data and Collection Methods**

Through the site, QualQuant Signals receives data that you actively submit as well as data that QualQuant Signals tracks:

_Actively Submitted Data:_ When you request information, subscribe to a mailing list or a service, register as a user, post to one of QualQuant Signals hosted forums or communities, send or respond to an online survey or otherwise actively send us data, QualQuant Signals usually collects data such as your name, email address(es), telephone number(s), country of residency, and certain information related to the business you represent (if any). 

_Passively Tracked Data:_ When you visit the site, QualQuant Signals also passively tracks information from your computer and Internet connection, such as the IP address of your computer, the date and time you access the site, the Internet address of web sites from which you link to our site, some of the computer technology you are using and your movements and preferences on our site. QualQuant Signals uses technology that many other web sites employ, including, without limitation, “cookies” or small data files stored on your computer’s hard drive, to collect information such as the aforementioned. In some instances, QualQuant Signals also uses cookies to collect information in connection with future visits from that web site, to recognize you as a previous visitor and to track your activity at our site. You do not need to have cookies turned on to participate in our surveys or to visit our site. You can refuse cookies by turning them off on your browser, but please note that this may adversely affect user experience and convenience.

_Combinations:_ Unless you actively submit personal information such as your name or address, passively tracked data does not typically allow QualQuant Signals to identify you personally (even though it can theoretically be done, QualQuant Signals does not try to find out who you are, unless you identify yourself voluntarily through an active submission of data). To the extent permitted by applicable law, QualQuant Signals reserves the right to combine passively tracked data or data available via a third party with personal data that you may choose to actively submit. QualQuant Signals does this on the [www.QualQuantSignals.com](http://www.qualquantsignals.com/) site and for some survey “panels” (which may be deployed on other sites). Specifically if you take surveys from QualQuant Signals, we will “fingerprint” your session in order to combat fraud. In generating this “fingerprint” QualQuant Signals gathers only publically available information from your browser; this includes your IP address, browser version, and other session information.

#### **Collection Purposes, Use of Data**

QualQuant Signals collects passively tracked data primarily for purposes of administering, protecting and improving our site and our systems, to better understand the preferences of our site visitors, to compile aggregated statistics about site usage, and to help personalize your experience on our site. QualQuant Signals also uses cookies and passively tracked data to protect the integrity of surveys, e.g., to prevent survey respondents from responding to the same survey twice.

For some survey panels, we will verify the information that you, or a third party, provide us and/or combine the information you provide with information QualQuant Signals may gather from additional sources. Verification of personal data may be done on our systems, or done by a third party. If your personal data is provided to us for verification purposes only QualQuant Signals will never store any of your personal information on our systems (QualQuant Signals store only the result of the verification process).

QualQuant Signals collects primarily for two purposes: Firstly, for the purpose for which you originally sent us the data e.g., to confirm your registration for a service, to run a survey, to allow you to run a survey, to bill for services or to send you information or materials that you requested – for additional information on our solutions please click here [http://www.QualQuantSignals.com/solutions/](http://www.qualquantsignals.com/ideation/); secondly, for purposes of informing you about products and services; you can opt out of receiving marketing emails as explained in Opt-Out below.

#### **Disclosures of Personal Information**

QualQuant Signals is not in the business of selling or renting your information to telemarketers and we do not share your personally identifiable information with others, except as follows:

If you use any QualQuant Signals services with a corporate email account (i.e., an account for employees, contractors, etc. as opposed to a personal email account with a general email service provider such as AOL, Hotmail, Yahoo, Gmail, etc.), and such corporation signs up for an enterprise account with us or is considering an enterprise account, QualQuant Signals may inform such corporation of your use of our service, so that you can benefit from enterprise pricing and any other benefits negotiated by the corporation for its registered users or otherwise arising from such coordination.

QualQuant Signals also engages agents and service providers who have access to data, but only to process such data on our behalf and for our purposes under confidentiality agreements.

QualQuant Signals may share your information as required by law or in the interest of protecting or exercising our or others’ legal rights, e.g., without limitation, in connection with requests from law enforcement officials and in connection with court proceedings.

QualQuant Signals may share or transfer your information in connection with a prospective or actual sale, merger, transfer or other reorganization of all or parts of our business.

QualQuant Signals reserves the right to use and disclose any information collected via the site that is not in personally identifiable form.

QualQuant Signals does not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information, (PII) with third parties for promotional purposes.

Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, note that QualQuant Signals will NOT share your identity or your individual responses to surveys that QualQuant Signals conducts itself with customers who may have commissioned such surveys; QualQuant Signals only provides aggregate response data to survey customers. But, as noted in the next following section, QualQuant Signals does not control how others may use our tools when they conduct surveys through our website.

#### **Third Party Data Collection Through Our Site**

When one of our users deploys our tools to send out survey requests or otherwise to collect data, such user will receive and process any responses. QualQuant Signals will host, but not access such information, except in connection with technical support or with the consent of the user who conducted the survey. QualQuant Signals posts rules on how our tools should be used, however, QualQuant Signals cannot control the data processing practices of our users and QualQuant Signals does not assume any responsibility for actions of our users who conduct surveys or of any other third parties.

#### **Co-branded Sites**

From time to time QualQuant Signals may partner with third parties to provide portions of a site. In the event that you provide personally identifiable information there, this privacy policy will continue to apply. You retain full rights to your data and may either contact us at [info@QualQuantSignals.com](mailto:info@QualQuantSignals.com) to change or remove your data or alternatively you may ask us for a contact at the third party who can provide this service.

#### **Opt-Out**

In connection with promotions or other projects, QualQuant Signals may ask you specifically whether you have objections against a certain kind of data use or sharing. If you opt-out under such circumstances, QualQuant Signals will respect your decision. **To opt-out of receiving further commercial emails, sharing of your information with our affiliates or to unsubscribe from services, please contact us at[privacy@QualQuantSignals.com](mailto:privacy@QualQuantSignals.com)**. Please note that our affiliates and other data recipients have their own data privacy policies, which may differ from ours and you would have to contact them separately with respect to opt-out requests.

#### **Access**

If personal information you have submitted through the site is no longer accurate, current, or complete, and you wish to update it , please update your profile on the site or send an email to [privacy@QualQuantSignals.com](mailto:privacy@QualQuantSignals.com). If you wish to delete your profile, please send an email to [privacy@QualQuantSignals.com](mailto:privacy@QualQuantSignals.com). Upon receipt of an appropriate request, QualQuant Signals will update or delete your information within 30 days, but QualQuant Signals reserves the right to use information previously obtained to verify your identity or take other actions that QualQuant Signals believes are appropriate.

#### **Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at . We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### **Blog**

Our Web site offers a publicly accessible blog. You should be aware that any information you provide in this area may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [info@QualQuantSignals.com](mailto:info@QualQuantSignals.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

#### **Security**

Transmissions over the Internet are never 100% secure or error-free. QualQuant Signals does, take reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. For example, QualQuant Signals encrypts your registration information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL follow this link <https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transport_Layer_Security>. It is your responsibility to safeguard any password and User ID you use to access the site and to notify us at [info@QualQuantSignals.com](mailto:info@QualQuantSignals.com) if you ever suspect that your password or User ID has been compromised. You are solely responsible for any unauthorized use of the site conducted via your password and User ID.

#### **Children’s Privacy.**

The site is intended for adults in the United States. QualQuant Signals does not intentionally or knowingly collect personally-identifiable information from children under the age of 13 and QualQuant Signals requests that individuals under the age of 13 not submit any personal information on the site.

#### **Terms of Use**

Your use of our site is governed by our Terms of Use, which contain disclaimers, limitations of liability, and a choice of New Jersey law and jurisdiction.

#### **Effective Date, Amendments**

This statement is effective as of 2015. QualQuant Signals reserves the right to change, modify, supplement or replace all or part of this statement from time to time and in our sole discretion, but will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the statement the date it was last updated. Before any material changes to this privacy policy QualQuant Signals will post a prominent notice on our home page no less than 30 days before these changes go into effect. When you visit the site, you are accepting the current version of this statement as posted on the site at that time. QualQuant Signals recommends that users revisit this statement on occasion to learn of any changes.

#### **Contact Us**

Please feel free to contact us with any comments, questions, complaints or suggestions you might have regarding the information practices described in this statement. You may send us an e-mail at [info@QualQuantSignals.com](mailto:info@QualQuantSignals.com) or QualQuant Signals , 1099 Wall Street West, Suite 138, Lyndhurst, NJ 07071.
